#02 "The Guild and the Receptionist"
Master
Newbie
Noir Stardia
16 years old
Level 33
Skills:
Great Sage
Get Creative
Editor
Bestow
LP Conversion
Stone Bullet
Discerning Eye
Noir Stardia
Headache Immunity
LP needed to Get Creative:
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Skills [Great Sage]
Skills [Get Creative] [Editor] [Bestow]
Skills [LP Conversion] [Stone Bullet]
Skills [Discerning Eye] [Headache Immunity]
Noir Stardia  LP.700
Noir Stardia  LP.400
Goblin
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Goblin  Lv.17
Sex: Male
Big Rabbit
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Emma Brightness  Lv.17
Skills [Dual-Wielded Daggers (Grade C)]
Skills [Wind Strike]
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Dual-Wielded Daggers (Grade B)
Needed to Get Creative  LP.300
Bestow to Emma              LP.400
Total Used                       LP.700
————————————————
Dual-Wielded Daggers (Grade C)
Improves wielder's handling of dual-wielded daggers
Using Editor to add "Significantly"
Editor Results
Dual-Wielded Daggers (Grade B)
Significantly improves wielder's
handling of dual-wielded daggers
LP used:
Noir Stardia
Skills [Dual-Wielded Daggers (Grade C)]
Skills [Wind Strike]
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Emma Brightness
Skills [Dual-Wielded Daggers (Grade B)]
Skills [Wind Strike]
m 0 0 l 0 -10 l 37 -10 b 39 -10 40 -9 40 -7 l 40 7 b 40 9 39 10 37 10 l -37 10 b -39 10 -40 9 -40 7 l -40 -7 b -40 -9 -39 -10 -37 -10 l 0 -10
Barbecue Is
a Battlefield.
by Emma Brightness
Noir Stardia
#03 "The Troubled Classmate"
Illustration: Tetsubuta